让我解释一下我看到这个布局时的
Let me the explain the reasoning that I use when I
推理过程。它看上去像有两个同等大小隔开的
look at a new layout. It looks like there's two equally spaced
列在这里。这表示我我们需要一个LinearLayout权重，
columns here. That signals to me we need LinearLayout weights,
其中的每一个都应该是等权的。所以我们来建立一个水平的
where each of these have equal weights. So let's create a horizontal
LinearLayout。在第一个图表里，我们有三个垂直堆叠的
LinearLayout. Within this first chart, we have three vertically stacked
文本框，所以我们现在有一个垂直的LinearLayout。同样
text views, so we have a vertical LinearLayout, and the same
处理有第二个图表，他有两个元素垂直地互相堆叠，
goes for this second chart which has two elements vertically stacked
这意味着我们同样用一个垂直的LinearLayout。
on top of each other, which means we use a vertical LinearLayout
这里是代码，我们在layout文件夹下创建一个
as well. And here's the code, we created a
new_list_item_forecasts_today XML文件
new_list_item_forecasts_today XML file under the layout folder.
代码看上去和list_item_forecast很相似。我
The code looks very similar to list_item_forecast. I
有一个水平的LinearLayout作为根节点。第一个
has a horizontal LinearLayout, as a root element. The first
子节点是一个垂直的LinearLayout，宽度是0
child is a vertical LinearLayout with the width zero
权值是1。第二个子节点是另外一个垂直的
and a weight of one. The second child is another vertical
LinearLayout，宽度是0，权重也是
LinearLayout with a width of zero and a weight
1，这样水平的空间将会在所有子节点中间
of one, that way the horizontal space will be distributed evenly
平均分布。如果你退回到第一个
among each child. If you go back to the first
LinearLayout，注意我们有三个文本框在
LinearLayout, notice that we have three TextViews within
其中，分别是日期，最高气温，最低气温。我们指明
it,for date, high temperature, and low temperature. We specify
中心应该在水平中央，所以在这个LinearLayout的一切
gravity to be center horizontal. So anything within the LinearLayout
都会水平居中对齐。否则，按照预设，他们应该
will be centered horizontally. Otherwise, by default, they would
在LinearLayout里靠左对齐。
be left aligned to the LinearLayout. The same applies
为第二个LinearLayout做相同的设定。我们指定中心应该在
for the second LinearLayout. We specify gravity to be
水平中间，这样里面的图标和天气预报的
center horizontal so that the icon and the weather forecast
TextView也会水平居中。
text view within it are also centered horizontally.